## Seth Akkerman

seth@sethakkerman.com

www.sethakkerman.com

I am a digital designer who likes to laugh with people. I have an insatiable curiosity and a desire to leave things better than I found them. I have a background in user experience design, user interface design, art direction, and marketing.

EDUCATION

SAVANNAH COLLEGE OF ART AND DESIGN, Savannah, Georgia

Graphic Design - Masters of Fine Arts, August 2009

UNIVERSITY OF CINCINNATI, Cincinnati, Ohio

Architectural Engineering Technology - Bachelor of Science, Cum Laude, June 2005

EXPERIENCE

**GAUGE,** Savannah, Georgia — Working Remotely from Chicago, Illinois UI and UX Designer, Illustrator, Motion Designer - October 2016–Present

Design eCommerce websites for a wide variety of industries. Prototype websites for client presentations and internal development handoff. Design and illustrate marketing materials for client websites, email, and social media. Illustrate articles written by Gauge team.

SAVANNAH COLLEGE OF ART AND DESIGN, Savannah, Georgia

Media & UX Designer, Art Director, eLearning - November 2010-September 2016

Designed and built individual websites for each SCAD eLearning course. Conceptualized and coded custom jQuery learning tools relating to course content. Captured and produced video, audio, and photography. Created hand and digital illustrations.

FREELANCE DESIGNER, Savannah, Georgia

Graphic Designer / Illustrator / Motion Designer - July 2009-Present

Select clients include Two Tides Brewing Co., SF Weekly, Mike Doughty / The Hornblow Group, The Pinyan Company, Telfair Museums, and Rowan Converse / Nocturne Records.

SKILLS / INTERESTS

**SKILLS** - Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign, After Effects, Premiere, InVision Prototyping, CSS, HTML5, jQuery, JavaScript, Git, GitHub, SASS, Sketch, Cinema 4D Lite, Processing

INTERESTS - Screen Printing, Woodblock Printing, Ping-Pong, Making Pizza

PUBLISHED

IdN Magazine, Volume 17, Number 5, 2010 - Spay and Neuter Commercial Featured

Designing Sustainable Packaging, Author: Scott Boylston, Bird Feeder Packaging Featured

AWARDS

2018 Print Magazine Regional Design Annual - Two Tides Brewing Co.
2010 Print Magazine Print in Motion - Finalist - Where the Wild Things Are
2010 ADDY Award - Silver - Telfair Ball Invitations
2009 UCDA Design Competition - Gold Medalist - Savannah Secession Series
American Greetings Scholarship for Excellence in Design (2008–2009)

SCAD Savannah Secession Graphic Design Exhibition Planning Committee (2008–2009)

SCAD Combined Honors Scholarship (2006–2009)

INVOLVEMENT / VOLUNTEERING

Creative Mornings Chicago - Communications Coordinator (2020–present) Creative Mornings Chicago - Event Day Volunteer (2019–present)

AIGA - Member (2006-present)

Type Director's Club - Member (2008-present)